screwattack.com 2007-12-15

# ScrewAttack.com- Something Original... Every Freakin' Day. Now with merchandise! *ding*

**Privacy Policy  
**

ScrewAttack Entertainment LLC, producer of ScrewAttack.com and its related content and service sites, believes that electronic privacy is crucial for the ongoing success of the Internet as a service, commercial, and entertainment medium. We know you're concerned about protecting your privacy online. At ScrewAttack.com, we treat your personal information (especially payment information) with the highest standards of safety, security, and confidentiality.  

**Information Gathered**

We don't collect personal information without your knowledge. We don't sell, rent, or give your personal information to unrelated third parties without your prior permission.  
This policy explains what information we collect about you and how we use that information. We also outline the choices you have.  

**ScrewAttack.com Store and ScrewAttack.com Subscriptions**

By shopping at ScrewAttack.com/merch.html or ScrewAttack.com/join.html, you accept the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.  
In order to ship products to you, we need to collect information about you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, e-mail address, home phone number and credit card information. We use your e-mail address as a login for the store, as well as a way to send you a confirmation of your order. If we have a question about your order, we may contact you by e-mail. For example, we may call you to verify your credit card information on a large purchase. We do this for your protection.

**Security**

ScrewAttack pledges a safe and worry-free shopping experience. We use the industry standard for Internet security, Secure Sockets Layer (SSL 128-bit) encryption to protect your personal data and ensure that it is transmitted securely.

**Traffic Data**

Each time a visitor comes to an ScrewAttack Entertainment LLC site, information is collected to improve the overall quality of ScrewAttack Entertainment LLC sites. ScrewAttack Entertainment LLC collects the visitor's domain name/IP Address (e.g., whether the user is logged on from netscape.com or yale.edu or 255.255.255.0), referral data (e.g., we record the address of the last URL a user visited prior to clicking through to an ScrewAttack Entertainment LLC site), and browser/platform type (e.g., a Netscape browser on a Macintosh platform).  
In addition to collecting these types of information, ScrewAttack Entertainment LLC's advertisement delivery system collects aggregate search terms for internal reporting and targeted advertising. ScrewAttack Entertainment LLC's advertisement delivery system collects visitor information for purposes of product monitoring, product improvement, and targeted advertising.  
ScrewAttack Entertainment LLC also counts, tracks, and aggregates the visitor's activity into our analysis of general traffic flow at ScrewAttack Entertainment LLC sites (e.g., tracking where traffic comes from and how traffic flows within the sites). ScrewAttack Entertainment LLC may merge this information into group data, which may then be shared on an aggregated basis with potential advertisers, research firms, and business partners. ScrewAttack Entertainment LLC will not disclose your individual identity or personal data. When ScrewAttack Entertainment LLC does present aggregated information to potential advertisers, research firms, and business partners, no one will be able to identify you or contact you.  

**E-mail Services**

Any/all e-mail addresses sent to us as the result of correspondence with the consumers of ScrewAttack Entertainment LLC will not be used or collected for the purposes of reselling to a third party and will not be added to a bulk e-mailing list.  
ScrewAttack Entertainment LLC provides users the opportunity to opt-in and opt-out of receiving e-mail communications from us. This is made available during sign-up for our e-mail lists and in e-mail messages delivered from ScrewAttack. For any list managed by ScrewAttack, users can use the link in the footer of most e-mail messages to unsubscribe.  

**User Submitted Content**

For all of your User Materials that you post or otherwise submit to the ScrewAttack.com, including feedback, bug reports, piracy reports or suggestions, you grant ScrewAttack Entertainment and the users of this ScrewAttack.com an unrestricted, irrevocable, non-exclusive, worldwide, royalty-free and fully paid up license under all Intellectual Property Rights to use, reproduce, publicly display, publicly perform, copy, edit, modify, translate, reformat, transmit and distribute such User Materials, with or without having your name attached to such Images, in any manner or form and for any purpose, with full rights to sublicense such rights through multiple tiers of distribution, and you also acknowledge and agree that ScrewAttack.com is free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how or techniques that you provide for any purpose without any compensation to you. You acknowledge and agree that ScrewAttack Entertainment LLC shall not be liable for any failure to store User Materials on the Site at any time.
